Sometimes the wrong side of the law is the right place to be.
American Outlaws is a western, action film directed by Les Mayfield.
When a Midwest town learns that a corrupt railroad baron has captured the deeds to their homesteads without
their knowledge, a group of young ranchers join forces to take back what is rightfully theirs.
They will become the object of the biggest manhunt in the history of the Old West and, as their fame
grows, so will the legend of their leader, a young outlaw by the name of Jesse James.
Jesse James, played by Colin Farrell.
Cole Younger, played by Scott Caan.
Zerelda "Zee" Mimms, played by Ali Larter.
Frank James, played by Gabriel Macht.
Jim Younger, played by Gregory Smith.
Thaddeus Rains, played by Harris Yulin.
American Outlaws is a 2001 American Western action film directed by Les
Mayfield and starring Colin Farrell, Scott Caan, and Ali Larter.
The film explores themes of sheriff, horse, outlaw, jesse james, cole younger.